<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<parent>
	<beginner>
		<levelOne>
			<goblin>
				<body>Svool! Uloold nv.</body>
				<body>Wouldn’t this game be easier if you knew what this new comer was saying? Use this key to decode what he said. </body>
				<body>A \ b \ c \ d \ e \ f \ g \ h \ i \ j \ k \ l \ m \ n \ o \ p \ q \ r \ s \ t \ u \ v \ w \ x \ y \ z &#10; Z\ y \ x \ w \ v \ u \ t \ s \ r \ q \ p \ o \ n \ m \ l \ k \ j \ i \ h \ g \ f \ e \ d \ c \ b \ a </body>
				<body>It says, “Hello! Follow me!”</body>
				<body>This was an example of learning the appropriate language to communicate.</body>
				<body>In this case, you learned the language to communicate with the alien.</body>
				<body>In programming, you will learn certain languages to communicate with the machine and other programmers.</body>
			</goblin>
		</levelOne>
		<levelTwoCave1>
			<instructions>
				<body>Oh no! You’re trapped in the forbidden cave! You have to figure out how to get out.</body>
				<body>This code looks important! Write it down so you don’t forget it.&#10;&#10;5fg4j685fg5u7x</body>
				<body>Here is a box of 20 torches. You can use them to light your way to the back of the cave.&#10;&#10;Press 'P' to drop a torch.</body>
			</instructions>
			<chest>
				<body>This treasure chest looks interesting! Try using the code from the entrance of the cave to see what is inside.</body>
				<body>Good job! You opened the chest. This was an example of writing to a file and reading from it.&#10;You read the unlock code, you stored it on a piece of paper, then you used it to open up the treasure chest.</body>
				<body>Inside the chest you found a key! Maybe it will fit in the door at the beginning of the cave.&#10;Go back following your torches and try it! </body>
			</chest>
		</levelTwoCave1>
		<levelThree>
			<MC>
				<introduction>
					<body>You got through the dark cave! Congratulations! Without the torches, you wouldn't have been able to&#10;find you way back. Their light guided you through unfamiliar territory.</body>
					<body>Like the torches, when you write code, comments will help you when you are lost. Code without comments&#10;is like trying to find your way back through a cave without torches: it would take you very long to make your&#10;way through the mysterious passages.</body>
					<body>By placing comments throughout your code, you help other programmers understand what your code is&#10;trying to accomplish. It can also help you remember why you wrote the code, saving you hours of heachaches.&#10;</body>
					<body>When writing code, make sure to use comments! Both you and others will thank you later for it.</body>
					<body>Now, you are on a new part of the island. As you move around the island, use yummy-looking&#10;objects to help you get through obstacles.</body>
					<body>To pick up an object, press the 'Space' key. To see information on the object, press and hold the 'I' key.</body>
				</introduction>
				<conclusion>
					<body>Wow, look at you! You found your way to the end of the level! Without the berries, you&#10;wouldn't have been able to accomplish this feat.</body>
					<body>Each berry gave you a special power that enhanced your ability to get through the level.&#10;You don't know how they did this, but they sure did!</body>
					<body>Berries are like objects in programming. Objects have different properties -- such as color,&#10;size, and weight -- and perform different functions -- such as change your speed and size.</body>
					<body>Objects are able to hide the steps they take to make these functions happen, similar to the&#10;mysteriousness of the berries. In future levels, you will learn more&#10;about objects and their benefits.</body>
					<body>But for now, you have completed the game. Well done! Please check our website in the future for updates to the game. Happy programming!</body>
				</conclusion>
			</MC>
			<guard>
				<endOfLevel>
					<body>Hey! You aren't allowed to be here! Beat it!</body>
				</endOfLevel>
			</guard>
		</levelThree>

<levelTwo>
     <popup-2.1>
        <body>Use your arrow keys to follow the alien up the path. </body>
     </popup-2.1>

     <popup-2.2>
       <body> Uh-oh! You have entered the forbidden cave! Take a look at the code used to create this
         level and think about why this might have happened:</body>

         <table>
           <tr>
             <td> moveLeft = </td>
             <td>move towards cave</td>
           </tr>
           <tr>
             <td> moveRight = </td>
             <td>move towards cave</td>
           </tr>
           <tr>
             <td> moveUp = </td>
             <td>move towards cave</td>
           </tr>
           <tr>
             <td> moveDown = </td>
             <td>move towards cave</td>
           </tr>
         </table>

     </popup-2.2>

     <popup-2.3>
       <body>You probably figured out that you went towards the cave
          because every command, regardless of its name, tells your
          character to move towards the cave. This is a bad example of naming.
          Your variables, in this case moveLeft, moveRight, moveUp,
          and moveDown, should be named according to their function.
           For example, moveDown should make the character move down, not move towards
           the cave.</body>
     </popup-2.3>
</levelTwo>

<levelThree>
    <popup-3.1>
      
    </popup-3.1>

    <popup-3.2>
      <body>To start, follow the arrow on the top of your screen. To place a torch, use the spacebar. To move, use your arrow keys. </body>
    </popup-3.2>

    <popup-3.3>
      <body>This treasure chest looks interesting!
        Try using the code from the entrance of the cave to see what is inside.</body>
    </popup-3.3>

    <popup-wrong>
      <body>Uh-oh, that wasn’t right. Try again!</body>
    </popup-wrong>

    <popup-right>
      <body>Good job! You opened the chest. This was an example of writing to a file and reading from it.
        You read the unlock code, you stored it on a piece of paper, then you used it to open up the treasure
        chest.  Inside the chest you found a key! Maybe it will fit in the door at the beginning of the cave.
        Go back following your torches and try it! </body>
    </popup-right>

  </levelThree>

<levelFour>
      <popup-4.1>
        <body>“Use the key to unlock the door!”</body>
      </popup-4.1>

      <popup-4.2>
        <body>“Good job! You’re free! Wasn’t escaping the cave easier with the torches to light your way than it would have
           been in the darkness? This shows you the importance of leaving comments in your code.
           Leaving comments helps remind you and tells other people what your code is meant to do. </body>
      </popup-4.2>

</levelFour>

</beginner>

<intermediate>
  <levelOne>
    <popup-1.1>
      <heading>Welcome to the beach!</heading>
      <body>Hey!! You didn’t follow me! Where have you been?</body>
    </popup-1.1>
	<popup-1.2>
      <popup-next>
        <body>No matter, your health is low! I ahve some berries to give you,
          but you'regoing to need to find more food quickly!</body>
		  </popup-next>
    </popup-1.2>

    <popup-1.3>
      <body> Click on each of the berries to eat them.</body>
    </popup-1.3>

      <popup-1.4>
        <body>As you probably noticed, each of those berries affected your health differently.
          While some gave you additional health, others took away some health.
          This is because each berry is an individual object. Each object has different properties and
          will do different things. You need more food. There was a fishing pole down the beach,
           maybe you could use that to catch yourself some dinner. </body>
      </popup-1.4>

  </levelOne>

  <levelTwo>
    <popup>
    <heading>Nice! You've found a fishing rod!</heading>
    <body>Go catch 10 fish so you can replenish your health!”</body>
    </popup>

    <popup-2.1>
      <body>“This seems to be taking a while. There is a net up the beach that might make this easier. Go find it.”</body>
    </popup-2.1>


  </levelTwo>

</intermediate>
</parent>